Finding aid for the Getty Center for Education in the Arts, Stephen M. Dobbs records, 1984-1989, undated (bulk 1987-1989) IA20027
Institutional Records and Archives
Stephen M. Dobbs records
1984-1989, undated (bulk 1987-1989)
1987-1989
Institutional Records and Archives
Getty Education Institute for the Arts
J. Paul Getty Trust
Getty Center for Education in the Arts
Dobbs, Stephen M.
IA20027
10 Linear Feet (24 boxes)
The records comprise the correspondence and subject files of Stephen M. Dobbs, Senior Program Officer for the Getty Center for Education in the Arts(GCEA), from 1987 to 1989. The records provide insight into the programs of the GCEA and its efforts to shape contemporary arts education in the United States through the development of the K-12 art education theory referred to as "discipline based art-education" (DBAE).
Related Materials Note
The following materials are offered as possible sources of further information on the people, programs, and subjects covered by the records. The listing is not exhaustive.
Publications
Dobbs, Stephen M. The DBAE Handbook: An Overview of Discipline Based Art Education. Santa Monica, Calif.: Getty Center for Education in the Arts. 1992.
Related Archival Materials
Art Education History Archives Project records, 1998-1999, Getty Education Institute for the Arts. Institutional Archives, Research Library, Getty Research Institute, Finding aid no. IA20034
Acquisition Information
2005.IA.14 was accessioned on October 25, 2005, the records are part of a defunct program and therefore fall under the custody of the Institutional Records and Archives Department. The records were recalled from Iron Mountain as a part of pilot testing the retention schedule roll-out in late October 2005.
Restrictions on Access
The records described in accession 2005.IA.14 are available for use by qualified researchers.
The following types of records are permanently closed: records containing personal information, records that compromise security or operations, legal communications, legal work product, and records related to donors. The J. Paul Getty Trust reserves the right to restrict access to any records held by the Institutional Archives.
Scope and Content of Collection
The records comprise outgoing letters with a few attached incoming letters, memoranda, proposals, notes, photocopies of checks, drafts, reports, resumes, agenda, printed materials, financial documents, iteneraries, and speeches dating from 1984 to 1989 (bulk 1987-1989), created and/or maintained by Stephen M. Dobbs, Senior Program Officer of the Getty Center for Education in the Arts (GCEA). Many of the outgoing letters were sent by Dobbs or his administrative assistant, Jerry Travers, to various professionals such as art specialists, art educators, curriculum supervisors, and classroom teachers on the subject of "discipline based art-education" (DBAE). Some letters include photocopies of checks for honoraria, presentations, and similar events. A substantial proportion of the internal letters and memoranda were sent to GCEA Director Lani Duke, as were Dobbs' monthly reports.
Among the subjects of the correspondence are Dobbs' work on contracts for contractors who carried out GCEA programs, specifically finding university contractors for pre-service extensions; CSSO Sunbird campus projects (CSU Foundation); ERIC – Art Education Project (Indiana University); drafts of, and comments on, a policy paper on perceptions of discipline-based arts education and the Getty Center; advisory committees correspondence; budget planning; staff retreats; children's television; translations of DBAE materials into Chinese; general announcements about developments elsewhere in the Getty; work with a public relations firm to advertise DBAE; regional art education institutes; grants of art related special initaitives; and the traveling done and speeches Dobbs delivered to discuss art education theories. Finally, the material also provides some indication of the research that Dobbs conducted toward writing several books and articles on the subject of DBAE.
Organization
These records are organized in two series:
Series I. Chronological correspondence, 1987-1989
Series II. Subject correspondence, 1984-1989.
Biography
Dr. Stephen Dobbs received his B.A. (1964) and Ph.D. (1972) from Stanford University. He first worked as a university professor in the humanities and, later in life, he became adjunct professor at San Francisco State University and an adjunct faculty member at the Institute for Jewish & Community Research.
He was a program analyst for the John D. Rockefeller III Fund and later joined the J. Paul Getty Trust. At the Getty Trust, as a Senior Program Officer of the Getty Center for Education in the Arts from September 1987 to September 1989, Dobbs' responsibilities centered around promoting a comprehensive approach to instruction and learning in art, called "discipline based art-education." DBAE, primarily developed for grades K through 12, focused on four foundational disciplines in art - art making, art criticism, art history and aesthetics - to encourage not only the creation of art, but also the understanding and appreciation of artistic processes and the role of art in society. Dobbs resigned on August 1, 1989; Philip Dunn took over his responsibilities.
Following his work at the Getty, Dobbs served as CEO of the Koret Foundation and the Marin Community Foundation. He later became the executive vice president of the Bernard Osher Foundation and also served as the executive director of the Taube Foundation for Jewish Life and Culture. Dobbs is also known for his work with Jewish community organizations. He is a former president of the Brandeis-Hillel Day School, vice president of the Bureau of Jewish Education, and vice president of Congregation Emanu-El. He was the founding director of the Jewish Community Federation of San Francisco Board of the Leadership Institute. He served as president of Mount Zion Health Fund and on the board of the Jewish Community Federation. In the general community, Dobbs served as director of Guide Dogs for the Blind and Words on Dance.
Administrative History
The Getty Center for Education in the Arts, later known as the Getty Education Institute for the Arts (GEI), was one of the original programs established by the J. Paul Getty Trust, an international cultural and philanthropic organization serving both general audiences and specialized professionals. The Trust is a not-for-profit institution, educational in purpose and character, that focuses on the visual arts in all of their dimensions. As of 2009 the Trust supports and oversees four programs: the J. Paul Getty Museum, the Getty Foundation, the Getty Conservation Institute, and the Getty Research Institute. The Trust founded the Getty Center for Education in the Arts in 1982 with the mission of improving the quality and status of arts education in the nation's public schools. The GEI's programs were guided by three premises: the visual arts should be an essential part of every child's education because knowledge of the arts is a principal means of understanding human experiences and transmitting cultural values; art education's content must be broadened to include instruction in art production, art history, art criticism, and aesthetics—an approach known as discipline-based art education (DBAE); and the most effective art education programs are based on partnerships among teachers, administrators, artists, museums, universities, and parents.
During its first ten years, the Getty Center for Education in the Arts / GEI concentrated on the implementation and dissemination of DBAE. This was achieved by advocating for the value of arts in education, through the dissemination of print publications and videotapes, national conferences, and collaborative projects; professional development for school and university personnel, through inservice programs such as the Los Angeles Institute; theory development to encourage evolution of DBAE, through seminars, doctoral fellowships, and the commissioning of scholarly publications; curriculum development to support creation of model instructional materials; and special initiatives to encourage others to champion DBAE. In January 1986 responsibility for administering arts education grants was transferred from the Trust's Grant Program to the Center for Education in the Arts. The goal of the arts education grant program was to support the development of model DBAE programs across the country. In addition to improving the quality of arts education in primary and secondary schools, the GEI also concentrated on the education of museum visitors. Focus group research and other studies resulted in a number of publications aimed at the museum community.
Lani Duke was the founding director of the Getty Center for Education in the Arts / GEI and continued to lead the program for 17 years. Duke resigned at the end of June, 1998 upon notice of the GEI's imminent dissolution. President Barry Muntiz named Ted Mitchell, former dean of the UCLA School of Education, as the Getty Trust's Vice President for Education and interim director of the GEI until the program's dissolution in 1999. When the Getty Education Institute for the Arts was dissolved one of its last projects was to record the legacy of its programs, most specifically the DBAE program, through interviews with leading arts educators of the time. The Center for Education in the Arts commissioned Dr. Stephen M. Dobbs in 1998 to conduct, record and transcribe these interviews.
Art -- Study and teaching; Art teachers -- Training of; Art museums -- Educational aspects; Art education in action; Correspondence; Memorandums; Notes; Reports; Drafts (documents); Agendas (administrative records); Speeches; Financial records; Proposals; Duke, Lani (Leilani Lattin)
- Chronological correspondence, 1987-1989; Series I.; 75 Linear Feet 15 boxes
  Arrangement
  The correspondence is arranged arranged in reverse chronological order.
  Scope and Contents note
  Records comprise outgoing letters with a few attached incoming letters, memoranda, proposals, notes, photocopies of checks, and reports, dating from 1987 to 1989, created and/or maintained by Stephen M. Dobbs, Senior Program Officer of the Getty Center for Education in the Arts (GCEA). Many of the outgoing letters were sent by Dobbs or his administrative assistant, Jerry Travers, to various professionals such as art specialists, curriculum supervisors, and classroom teachers on the subject of "discipline based art-education" (DBAE). These letters can include photocopies of checks for honoraria, presentations, and similar events (the account numbers may be restricted). A substantial proportion of the internal letters and memoranda were sent to Education Institute Director Lani Duke, as were the Dobbs' monthly reports, which appear periodically. Among the subjects of the correspondence are Dobbs' work on contracts for contractors who carried out GCEA programs such as, for example, finding university contractors for pre-service extensions, CSSO Sunbird campus projects (CSU Foundation), and ERIC – Art Education Project (Indiana University). Finally, the material also provides some indication of the research that Dobbs conducted toward writing several books and articles on the subject of DBAE.
  The records include Dobbs' August 1, 1989 resignation letter, saying he will leave at the end of the summer (Sept. 1), though the records continue until September 25 while he finished out his role on a planning committee. Philip Dunn took over Dobbs' responsibilities when he left.
  - September 25, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 1)
  - September 22, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 2)
  - September 1, 1989, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 3-4)
  - August 30, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 5)
  - August 21-24, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 6)
  - August 18, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 7)
  - August 17, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 8)
  - August 15-16, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 9)
  - August 11, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 10)
  - August 9-10, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 11)
  - August 8, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 12)
  - August 4, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 13)
  - August 3, 1989, [3 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 14-16)
  - August 1-2, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-1, Folder 17)
  - July 27-31, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 1)
  - July 25, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 2)
  - July 20-24, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 3)
  - July 14-19, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 4)
  - July 11-13, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 5)
  - July 5, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 6)
  - June 30, 1989, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 7-8)
  - June 26, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 9)
  - June 22-23, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 10)
  - June 20-21, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 11)
  - June 15-16, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 12)
  - June 13, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 13)
  - June 12, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 14)
  - June 9, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 15)
  - June 5-6, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 16)
  - June 2, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 17)
  - June 1, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 18)
  - May 30, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 19)
  - May 31, 1989, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 20-21)
  - May 25, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-2, Folder 22)
  - May 23, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 1)
  - May 22, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 2)
  - May 17-19, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 3)
  - May 15-16, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 4)
  - May 10-12, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 5)
  - May 4-9, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 6)
  - May 3, 1989, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 7-8)
  - May 1-2, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 9)
  - April 21-28, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 10)
  - April 19-20, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 11)
  - April 17, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 12)
  - April 14, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 13)
  - April 13, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 14)
  - April 6-12, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 15)
  - April 5, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 16)
  - April 3-4, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-3, Folder 17)
  - March 31, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 1)
  - March 30, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 2)
  - March 29, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 3)
  - March 28, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 4)
  - March 22-23, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 5)
  - March 21, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 6)
  - March 20, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 7)
  - March 17, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 8)
  - March 15-16, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 9)
  - March 13-14, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 10)
  - March 9-10, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 11)
  - March 7-8, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 12)
  - March 2-3, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 13)
  - March 1, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 14)
  - February 28, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 15)
  - February 24, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-4, Folder 16)
  - February 23, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 1)
  - February 22, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 2)
  - February 21, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 3)
  - February 16-17, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 4)
  - February 15, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 5)
  - February 14, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 6)
  - February 13, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 7)
  - February 10, 1989, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 8-9)
  - February 6-9, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 10)
  - February 1, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 11)
  - January 30-31, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 12)
  - January 26-27, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 13)
  - January 25, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 14)
  - January 24, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-5, Folder 15)
  - January 20, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 1)
  - January 17-18, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 2)
  - January 12-13, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 3)
  - January 11, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 4)
  - January 9-10, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 5)
  - January 5, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 6)
  - January 3-4, 1989 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 7)
  - December 29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 8)
  - December 27-28, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 9)
  - December 23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 10)
  - December 22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 11)
  - December 21, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 12)
  - December 14-16, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 13)
  - December 9-12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 14)
  - December 5-7, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 15)
  - December 1-2, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 16)
  - November 22-23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-6, Folder 17)
  - November 21, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 1)
  - November 17, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 2)
  - November 16, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 3)
  - November 14-15, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 4)
  - November 11, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 5)
  - November 10, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 6)
  - November 9, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 7)
  - November 8, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 8)
  - November 1-4, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 9)
  - October 27-28, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 10)
  - October 25-26, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 11)
  - October 20-24, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 12)
  - October 17-19, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 13)
  - October 13, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 14)
  - October 10-12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 15)
  - October 6-7, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 16)
  - October 3-4, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 17)
  - September 28, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 18)
  - September 26-27, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 19)
  - September 19-20, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 20)
  - September 15-16, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 21)
  - September 14, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 22)
  - September 12-13, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-7, Folder 23)
  - September 9, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 1)
  - September 7-8, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 2)
  - September 6, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 3)
  - September 2, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 4)
  - September 1, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 5)
  - August 30-31, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 6)
  - August 29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 7)
  - August 26, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 8)
  - August 24-25, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 9)
  - August 22-23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 10)
  - August 18-19, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 11)
  - August 16-17, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 12)
  - August 15, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 13)
  - August 11-12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 14)
  - August 4-5, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 15)
  - August 1-3, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 16)
  - July 26-29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 17)
  - July 25, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-8, Folder 18)
  - July 20-22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 1)
  - July 19, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 2)
  - July 18, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 3)
  - July 13-15, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 4)
  - July 8, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 5)
  - July 6, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 6)
  - July 1-5, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 7)
  - June 30, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 8)
  - June 29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 9)
  - June 28, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 10)
  - June 27, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 11)
  - June 24, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 12)
  - June 23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 13)
  - June 22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 14)
  - June 20-21, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 15)
  - June 16-17, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-9, Folder 16)
  - June 15, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 1)
  - June 14, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 2)
  - June 13, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 3)
  - June 8-10, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 4)
  - May 27, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 5)
  - May 25-26, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 6)
  - May 23-24, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 7)
  - May 16-19, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 8)
  - May 13, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 9)
  - May 11-12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 10)
  - May 10, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 11)
  - May 9, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 12)
  - May 6, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 13)
  - May 5, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 14)
  - May 3, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 15)
  - May 2, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 16-17)
  - April 28, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-10, Folder 18-19)
  - April 26-27, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 1)
  - April 22-25, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 2)
  - April 19-20, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 3)
  - April 18, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 4)
  - April 15, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 5)
  - April 14, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 6)
  - April 11-13, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 7)
  - April 5-7, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 8)
  - April 4, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 9)
  - April 2, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 10)
  - March 30, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 11-12)
  - March 28-29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 13)
  - March 25, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 14)
  - March 24, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 15)
  - March 23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 16)
  - March 22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 17)
  - March 21, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-11, Folder 18)
  - March 18, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 1)
  - March 17, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 2)
  - March 16, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 3)
  - March 12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 4)
  - March 11, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 5-6)
  - March 10, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 7)
  - March 9, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 8-9)
  - March 8, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 10-11)
  - March 7, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 12)
  - March 4, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 13-14)
  - March 3, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 15)
  - March 2, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 16)
  - March 1, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 17)
  - February 29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 18)
  - February 26, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 19)
  - February 25, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 20-21)
  - February 24, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 22)
  - February 23, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 23)
  - February 22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 24)
  - February 18, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-12, Folder 25-26)
  - February 17, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 1-2)
  - February 16, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 3-4)
  - February 12, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 5)
  - February 11, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 6-7)
  - February 9, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 8)
  - February 1, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 9)
  - January 30, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 10)
  - January 29, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 11)
  - January 28, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 12)
  - January 26, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 13)
  - January 25, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 14)
  - January 22, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 15)
  - January 21, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 16)
  - January 20, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 17)
  - January 19, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 18-19)
  - January 14, 1988 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 20)
  - January 13, 1988, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 21-22)
  - December 29, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 23)
  - December 28, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 24)
  - December 23, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-13, Folder 25)
  - December 22, 1987, [2 folders] (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 1-2)
  - December 21, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 3)
  - December 18, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 4)
  - December 17, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 5)
  - December 15, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 6)
  - December 14, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 7)
  - December 11, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 8)
  - December 10, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 9)
  - December 9, 1987 (Box 2005.IA.14-14, Folder 10)